{
    "cc111": [
        {
            "question_num": "q1",
            "question": "What was Meta Platforms Inc formerly known as?",
            "correct_answer": "b",
            "a": "Youtube",
            "b": "Facebook",
            "c": "Twitter",
            "d": "TikTok"
        },
        {
            "question_num": "q2",
            "question": "The logo for luxury car maker Porsche features which animal?",
            "correct_answer": "a",
            "a": "Horse",
            "b": "Pig",
            "c": "Dog",
            "d": "Chicken"
        },
        {
            "question_num": "q3",
            "question": "Which element is said to keep bones strong?",
            "correct_answer": "d",
            "a": "Protein",
            "b": "Calories",
            "c": "Fats",
            "d": "Calcium"
        },
        {
            "question_num": "q4",
            "question": "Suriname is located on which continent?",
            "correct_answer": "a",
            "a": "South America",
            "b": "North America",
            "c": "South Africa",
            "d": "West Virginia"
        },
        {
            "question_num": "q5",
            "question": "In tennis, what piece of fruit is found at the top of the men’s Wimbledon trophy?",
            "correct_answer": "b",
            "a": "Apple",
            "b": "Pineapple",
            "c": "Grapes",
            "d": "Mango"
        },
        {
            "question_num": "q6",
            "question": "What is a female elephant called?",
            "correct_answer": "a",
            "a": "Cow",
            "b": "Bear",
            "c": "Deer",
            "d": "Mamoth"
        },
        {
            "question_num": "q7",
            "question": "Franz Josef Strauss Airport is located in which country?",
            "correct_answer": "a",
            "a": "Germany",
            "b": "Norway",
            "c": "Italy",
            "d": "France"
        },
        {
            "question_num": "q8",
            "question": "Which is the only planet in our solar system not named after a Roman or Greek god?",
            "correct_answer": "d",
            "a": "Jupiter",
            "b": "Mars",
            "c": "Saturn",
            "d": "Earth"
        },
        {
            "question_num": "q9",
            "question": "In which sport is the Davis Cup contested?",
            "correct_answer": "c",
            "a": "Basketball",
            "b": "Badminton",
            "c": "Tennis",
            "d": "Golf"
        },
        {
            "question_num": "q10",
            "question": "‘The Beach’ starring Leonardo DiCaprio is set in which country?",
            "correct_answer": "b",
            "a": "Singapore",
            "b": "Thailand",
            "c": "Vietnam",
            "d": "Malaysia"
        }
    ]
}